HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm. 6199/012 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm
1941-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
HERE Joint Executive Board.
6199/012 mf
2.89 cubic feet
26 microfilm reels
Reports, minutes, correspondence, microfilm.
8255114
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 07, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 07, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE); HERE Joint Executive Board
8255114
- Fairbanks, AK. Correspondence., 1947-1970; 1 (Reel 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Beginning at location 000.
- Fairbanks, AK. International Audits., 1958-1970; 2 (Reel 1)
- Juneau, AK. Correspondence., 1954-1975; 3 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at location 006.
- Juneau, AK. International Audits., 1959-1977; 4 (Reel 1)
- Miami, AZ. Correspondence., 1965; 5 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at location 014.
- Miami, AZ. International Audits., 1959-1965; 6 (Reel 1)
- Tucson, AZ. Correspondence., 1953-1974; 7 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at location 017.
- Tucson, AZ. International Audits., 1942-1974; 8 (Reel 1)
- Eureka, CA. Correspondence., 1960-1971; 9 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at location 067.
- Eureka, CA. International Audits., 1956-1971; 10 (Reel 1)
- Fresno, CA. Correspondence., 1947-1967; 11 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at location 101.
- Fresno, CA. International Audits., 1941-1947; 12 (Reel 1)
- Los Angeles, CA. Jurisdiction and By-Laws., 13 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at location 114.5.
- Los Angeles, CA. Correspondence., 1946-1960; 14 (Reel 1)
- Los Angeles, CA. Trustees. Correspondence., 1961-1964; 1 (Reel 2)
- Los Angeles, CA. Trustees. Correspondence., 1965; 2 (Reel 2)
- Los Angeles, CA. Trustees. Correspondence., 1966; 3 (Reel 2)
- Los Angeles, CA. Trustees. Correspondence., 1967; 4 (Reel 2)
- Los Angeles, CA. Trustees. Correspondence., 1967-1970; 1 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Trustees. Correspondence., 1971-1978; 2 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Jurisdictional Lines., 1956; 3 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Dispute between L.U.#17 and L.U.#639., 4 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Jurisdiction Dispute R.C.I.A. vs. LA JEB., 5 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Joe Lewis Independent Union., 6 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Jurisdiction Dispute R.C.I.A. Local Union - LA JEB., 7 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Jurisdictional Dispute. L.U.#17 and L.U.#440., 8 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Jurisdictional Dispute. L.U.#440 and L.U.#765., 9 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Calabasas Inn., 10 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. R.C.I.A. Ralph's Grocery Chain. Case #70-54., 11 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. Ralph's Grocery Chain. Appeal by R.C.I.A., 12 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. AFL-CIO Raid. S.E.I.U. vs. L.U.#440. Case #72-59., 13 (Reel 3)
- Los Angeles, CA. International Audits., 1943-1978; 14 (Reel 3)
- Oakland, CA. Correspondence., 1948-1977; 1 (Reel 4)
- Oakland, CA. Associated Hospitals of the East Bay, Inc. L.U.#31. Case #65-60., 2 (Reel 4)
- Oakland, CA. Denny's Restaurants., 3 (Reel 4)
- Oakland, CA. International Audits., 1941-1976; 4 (Reel 4)
- Sacramento, CA. Correspondence., 1961-1974; 5 (Reel 4)
  Beginning at location 190.
- Sacramento, CA. International Audits., 1942-1975; 6 (Reel 4)
- San Francisco, CA. Correspondence., 1945-1965; 1 (Reel 5)
- San Francisco, CA. Correspondence., 1966-1968; 2 (Reel 5)
- San Francisco, CA. Correspondence., 1969-1971; 3 (Reel 5)
- San Francisco, CA. Correspondence., 1972; 4 (Reel 5)
- San Francisco, CA. Correspondence., 1972-1977; 1 (Reel 6)
- San Francisco, CA. International Audits., 1941-1976; 2 (Reel 6)
- San Mateo, CA. International Audits., 1941-1943; 3 (Reel 6)
  Beginning at location 072.
- San Pedro, CA, Correspondence., 1946-1973; 4 (Reel 6)
  Beginning at location 073.
- San Pedro, CA, International Audits., 1942-1973; 5 (Reel 6)
- Stockton, CA. Correspondence., 1950-1974; 6 (Reel 6)
  Beginning at location 107.
- Stockton, CA. International Audits., 1942-1974; 7 (Reel 6)
- Denver, CO. Correspondence., 1952-1964; 8 (Reel 6)
  Beginning at location 139.5.
- Denver, CO. International Audits., 1943-1965; 9 (Reel 6)
- Washington, DC. Hotel Strike., 1946; 10 (Reel 6)
  Beginning at location 175.
- Washington, DC. Correspondence., 1947-1970; 11 (Reel 6)
- Washington, DC. Correspondence., 1971; 12 (Reel 6)
- Washington, DC. Correspondence., 1971-1978; 1 (Reel 7)
- Washington, DC. Gratuity Distribution in Hospitality Suites., 2 (Reel 7)
- Washington, DC. Termination of Trusteeship., 3 (Reel 7)
- Washington, DC. International Audits., 1951-1978; 4 (Reel 7)
- Miami Beach, FL. Correspondence., 1958-1974; 5 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at location 093.
- Miami Beach, FL. International Audits., 1958-1974; 6 (Reel 7)
- Peoria, IL. Correspondence., 1947-1977; 7 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at location 099.
- Peoria, IL. Loan Repayments., 8 (Reel 7)
- Peoria, IL. International Audits., 1950-1977; 9 (Reel 7)
- Madison & St. Claire County, IL. International Audits., 1958-1960; 10 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at location 134.
- Terre Haute, IN. Correspondence., 1955-1968; 11 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at location 135.
- Terre Haute, IN. International Audits., 1960-1968; 12 (Reel 7)
- Baltimore, MD. Correspondence., 1949-1951; 13 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at location 140.
- Baltimore, MD. International Audits., 1951-1956; 14 (Reel 7)
- Boston, MA.. Correspondence., 1946-1976; 15 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at location 144.5.
- Boston, MA.. International Audits., 1951-1976; 16 (Reel 7)
- Lawrence, MA.. Correspondence., 1959-1976; 17 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at location 225.5.
- Lawrence, MA.. International Audits., 1951-1975; 18 (Reel 7)
- Springfield, MA. Correspondence., 1949-1950; 19 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at location 233.
- Springfield, MA. International Audits., 1951-1956; 20 (Reel 7)
- Detroit, MI. Jurisdiction File., 1 (Reel 8)
- Detroit, MI. Correspondence., 1943-1974; 2 (Reel 8)
- Detroit, MI. Hotel Strike., 1965; 3 (Reel 8)
- Detroit, MI. Howard Johnson Co. vs. Detroit J.E.B. Case #74-631., 4 (Reel 8)
- Detroit, MI. International Audits., 1950-1974; 5 (Reel 8)
- Port Huron, MI. Correspondence., 1961; 6 (Reel 8)
  Beginning at location 081.
- Port Huron, MI. International Audits., 1959-1961; 7 (Reel 8)
- Duluth, MN. Correspondence., 1946-1975; 8 (Reel 8)
  Beginning at location 082.5.
- Duluth, MN. International Audits., 1944-1973; 9 (Reel 8)
- Jefferson City, MO. Correspondence., 1958-1977; 10 (Reel 8)
- Jefferson City, MO. International Audits., 1960-1977; 11 (Reel 8)
- Kansas City, MO. Correspondence., 1948-1977; 12 (Reel 8)
  Beginning at location 117.5.
- Kansas City, MO. International Audits., 1942-1974; 13 (Reel 8)
- St. Louis, MO. Correspondence., 1942-1975; 1 (Reel 9)
- St. Louis, MO. International Audits., 1942-1974; 2 (Reel 9)
- Springfield, MO. Correspondence., 1961-1962; 3 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 110.
- Springfield, MO. International Audits., 1956-1962; 4 (Reel 9)
- Bozeman, MT. Correspondence., 1971-1976; 5 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 117.
- Bozeman, MT. International Audits., 1972-1975; 6 (Reel 9)
- Great Falls, MT. Correspondence., 1971-1976; 7 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 120.
- Great Falls, MT. International Audits., 1972-1975; 8 (Reel 9)
- Havre, MT. Correspondence., 1956-1959; 9 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 137.5.
- Havre, MT. International Audits., 1958-1970; 10 (Reel 9)
- Kalispell, MT. Correspondence., 1964-1966; 11 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 141.5.
- Kalispell, MT. International Audits., 1964-1966; 12 (Reel 9)
- Livingston, MT. Correspondence., 1959-1970; 13 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 143.5.
- Livingston, MT. International Audits., 1943-1970; 14 (Reel 9)
- Missoula, MT. Correspondence., 1952-1970; 15 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 149.
- Missoula, MT. International Audits., 1958-1970; 16 (Reel 9)
- Reno, NV. Correspondence., 1946-1970; 17 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 155.
- Reno, NV. International Audits., 1948-1968; 18 (Reel 9)
- Atlantic City, NJ. Correspondence., 1947-1974; 19 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at location 211.5.
- Atlantic City, NJ. International Audits., 1951-1974; 20 (Reel 9)
- Hoboken, NJ. Correspondence., 1945-1963; 1 (Reel 10)
- Hoboken, NJ. Defaulting Secretary Peter J. Born., 2 (Reel 10)
- Hoboken, NJ. International Audits., 1951-1968; 3 (Reel 10)
- Jersey City, NJ. Correspondence., 1967-1977; 4 (Reel 10)
  Beginning at location 012.
- Jersey City, NJ. International Audits., 1974-1976; 5 (Reel 10)
- Newark, NJ. Correspondence., 1948-1977; 6 (Reel 10)
  Beginning at location 018.5.
- Newark, NJ. Trustee Howard H. Rovner., 7 (Reel 10)
- Newark, NJ. International Audits., 1951-1977; 8 (Reel 10)
- Trenton, NJ. International Audits., 1958-1961; 9 (Reel 10)
  Beginning at location 070.5.
- Binghamton, NY. International Audits., 1956-1958; 10 (Reel 10)
- Brooklyn, NY. Correspondence., 1941-1975; 11 (Reel 10)
  Beginning at location 073.5.
- Brooklyn, NY. International Audits., 1948-1975; 12 (Reel 10)
- Buffalo, NY. Correspondence., 1948-1976; 13 (Reel 10)
  Beginning at location 121.
- Buffalo, NY. International Audits., 1950-1977; 14 (Reel 10)
- New York, NY. Jurisdiction File., 15 (Reel 10)
  Beginning at location 168.
- New York, NY. Trusteeship File., 16 (Reel 10)
- New York, NY. Correspondence., 1935-1959; 17 (Reel 10)
- New York, NY. Correspondence., 1961-1964; 18 (Reel 10)
- New York, NY. Correspondence., 1964-1977; 1 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. Howard Johnson File., 2 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. Howard Johnson International Contract Protests against it., 3 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. Howard Johnson Case., 4 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. Survey. Re: Resolutions of Convention Proceedings., 5 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. Matters Submitted to Executive Board, Miami, FL., 6 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. Prado Restaurant., 7 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. Brass Rail. Jurisdictional Dispute., 8 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. Allied Trades Council L.U.#254 Dispute., 9 (Reel 11)
- New York, NY. International Audits., 1951-1977; 10 (Reel 11)
- Rochester, NY. Correspondence., 1949-1969; 11 (Reel 11)
  Beginning at location 205.
- Rochester, NY. International Audits., 1950-1968; 12 (Reel 11)
- Syracuse, NY. Correspondence., 1957-1968; 1 (Reel 12)
- Syracuse, NY. International Audits., 1950-1967; 2 (Reel 12)
- Cincinnati, OH. Correspondence., 1936-1972; 3 (Reel 12)
  Beginning at location 012.5.
- Cincinnati, OH. International Audits., 1950-1972; 4 (Reel 12)
- Cleveland, OH. Correspondence., 1943-1968; 5 (Reel 12)
  Beginning at location 137.
- Cleveland, OH. Defaulting Secretary William J. Pierce., 6 (Reel 12)
- Cleveland, OH. Trusteeship., 7 (Reel 12)
- Cleveland, OH. Trustee M. A. Kenney., 8 (Reel 12)
- Cleveland, OH. International Audits., 1955-1968; 9 (Reel 12)
- Dayton, OH. International Audits., 1956-1964; 10 (Reel 12)
  Beginning at location 174.
- Portland, OR. Correspondence., 1951-1965; 11 (Reel 12)
  Beginning at location 177.5.
- Portland, OR. Correspondence., 1966-1969; 12 (Reel 12)
- Portland, OR. Correspondence., 1970-1977; 1 (Reel 13)
- Portland, OR. International Audits., 1941-1977; 2 (Reel 13)
- Pittsburgh, PA. Correspondence., 1947-1977; 3 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 098.5.
- Pittsburgh, PA. International Audits., 1950-1974; 4 (Reel 13)
- Scranton, PA. Correspondence., 1947-1970; 5 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 112.
- Scranton, PA. International Audits., 1951-1970; 6 (Reel 13)
- Tacoma, WA. Correspondence., 1963-1978; 7 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 130.
- Tacoma, WA. International Audits., 1960-1977; 8 (Reel 13)
- Yakima, WA. Correspondence., 1960-1975; 9 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 155.5.
- Yakima, WA. International Audits., 1960-1975; 10 (Reel 13)
- Janesville, WI. Correspondence., 1954-1972; 11 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 180.
- Janesville, WI. International Audits., 1951-1964; 12 (Reel 13)
- Kenosha, WI. International Audits., 1957-1958; 13 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 184.
- Milwaukee, WI. Correspondence., 1961-1963; 14 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 185.5.
- Milwaukee, WI. International Audits., 1957-1962; 15 (Reel 13)
- Cheyenne, WY. Correspondence., 1952-1974; 16 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 189.
- Cheyenne, WY. International Audits., 1941-1975; 17 (Reel 13)
- Laramie, WY. Correspondence., 1963-1972; 18 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 201.
- Laramie, WY. International Audits., 1952-1968; 19 (Reel 13)
- Rock Springs, WY. Correspondence., 1955-1966; 20 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at location 207.
- Rock Springs, WY. International Audits., 1941-1965; 21 (Reel 13)
- Calgary Alta, Canada. Correspondence., 1957-1970; 1 (Reel 14)
- Calgary Alta, Canada. International Audits., 1945-1968; 2 (Reel 14)
- Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. Correspondence., 1957-1975; 3 (Reel 14)
  Beginning at location 005.5.
- Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. International Audits., 1945-1976; 4 (Reel 14)
- Montreal, Quebec, Canada. Correspondence., 1943-1978; 5 (Reel 14)
  Beginning at location 021.
- Montreal, Quebec, Canada. Trustee Richard C. Uhrich., 6 (Reel 14)
- Montreal, Quebec, Canada. International Audits., 1946-1978; 7 (Reel 14)
- Niagara Falls and St. Catherines, Ontario, Canada. International Audits., 1958; 8 (Reel 14)
  Beginning at location 052.
- California., 1 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 0005.
- Long Beach, CA. By-Laws and Jurisdiction., 2 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 0006.
- Long Beach, CA. Correspondence., 1948-1963; 3 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 0054.
- Long Beach, CA. Correspondence., 1964-1966; 4 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 0339.
- Long Beach, CA. North American Aviation, Inc. Gladieux Food Service., 1967; 5 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 0637.
- Long Beach, CA. North American Aviation, Inc. Gladieux Food Service., 1967-1969; 6 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 0824.
- Long Beach, CA. North American Aviation, Inc. Gladieux Food Service., 1970-1981; 7 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1078.
- Long Beach, CA. Maritime Cooks and Stewards. Dispute., 1971; 8 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1251.
- Long Beach, CA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 9 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1286.
- Long Beach, CA. International Audit Reports., 10 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1352.
- Los Angeles, CA., 11 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1488.
- Los Angeles, CA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 12 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1489.
- Oakland, CA., 13 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1670.
- Oakland, CA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 14 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1671.
- Sacramento, CA., 15 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1770.
- Sacramento, CA. Article XX. SEIU vs. JEB. Case #72-75., 16 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1771.
- Sacramento, CA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 17 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1805.
- San Diego, CA., 18 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1873.
- San Diego, CA. Jurisdiction., 19 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1874.
- San Diego, CA. Jurisdiction., 1942-1963; 20 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at location 1878.
- San Diego, CA. (continued), 1 (Reel 16)
- San Diego, CA. Correspondence., 1964-1969; 2 (Reel 16)
- San Diego, CA. Correspondence., 1970-1973; 3 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 0499.
- San Diego, CA. Correspondence., 1974-1979; 4 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 1195.
- San Diego, CA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 5 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 1446.
- San Diego, CA. International Audit Reports., 6 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 1589.
- San Francisco, CA., 7 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 1744.
- San Francisco. CA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 8 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 1745.
- San Jose, CA., 9 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 1834.
- San Jose, CA., 1961-1969; 10 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 1835.
- San Jose, CA., 1970-1978; 11 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at location 2256.
- San Jose, CA., 1 (Reel 17)
- San Jose, CA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 2 (Reel 17)
- San Jose, CA. International Audit Reports., 3 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0079.
- Southern California., 4 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0153.
- Southern California. Correspondence., 1977-1978; 5 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0154.
- Southern California. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 6 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0203.
- Stockton, CA., 7 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0217.
- Stockton, CA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 8 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0218.
- Edmonton, Alberta, Canada., 9 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0263.
- Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 10 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0264.
- Montreal, Quebec, Canada., 11 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0333.
- Montreal, Quebec, Canada. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 12 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0334.
- Montreal, Quebec, Canada. International Audit Reports., 13 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0471.
- Toronto, Ontario, Canada., 14 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0478.
- Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Jurisdiction., 15 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0479.
- Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Correspondence., 1959-1980; 16 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0599.
- Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 17 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 0764.
- Toronto, Ontario, Canada. International Audit Reports., 18 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1029.
- Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada., 19 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1121.
- Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada., 1953-1981; 20 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1122.
- Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 21 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1595.
- Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada. International Audit Reports., 22 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1612.
- Washington, DC., 23 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1719.
- Washington, DC. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 24 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1720.
- Peoria, IL., 25 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1765.
- Peoria, IL. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 26 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1766.
- Boston, MA., 27 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1854.
- Boston, MA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 28 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1855.
- Lawrence, MA., 29 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1929.
- Lawrence, MA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 30 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 1930.
- Duluth, MN., 31 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 2067.
- Duluth, MN. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 32 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at location 2068.
- Minneapolis, MN., 1 (Reel 18)
- Minneapolis, MN. Correspondence., 1950-1969; 2 (Reel 18)
- Minneapolis, MN. Correspondence., 1970-1978; 3 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 0597.
- Minneapolis, MN. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 4 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1080.
- Minneapolis, MN. International Audit Reports., 5 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1248.
- St. Paul, MN., 6 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1363.
- St. Paul, MN., 1946-1976; 7 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1364.
- St. Paul, MN. JEB Shortages. P.A. Farrel & Ed Barrett: Secretary & President., 1951-1952; 8 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1669.
- St. Paul, MN. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 9 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1696.
- St. Paul, MN. International Audit Reports., 10 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1779.
- Jefferson City, MO., 11 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1866.
- Jefferson City, MO. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 12 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1867.
- St. Louis, MO., 13 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1872.
- St. Louis, MO. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 14 (Reel 18)
- Billings, MT., 15 (Reel 18)
- Billings, MT., 1945-1979; 16 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 1931.
- Billings, MT. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 17 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 2224.
- Billings, MT. International Audit Reports., 18 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 2347.
- Bozeman, MT., 19 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 2444.
- Bozeman, MT. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 20 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 2445.
- Bozeman, MT. International Audit Reports., 21 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at location 2530.
- Butte, MT., 1 (Reel 19)
- Butte, MT. Correspondence., 1954-1982; 2 (Reel 19)
- Butte, MT. International Audit Reports., 3 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0085.
- Great Falls, MT., 4 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0156.
- Great Falls, MT. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 5 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0157.
- Helena, MT., 6 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0209.
- Helena, MT., 1942-1982; 7 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0210.
- Helena, MT. International Audit Reports., 8 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0267.
- Atlantic City, NJ., 9 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0323.
- Atlantic City, NJ. Jurisdiction., 10 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0324.
- Atlantic City, NJ., 1979-1980; 11 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0330.
- Atlantic City, NJ. Trusteeship. Frank Gerace, International Trustee., 1979-1980; 12 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0364.
- Atlantic City, NJ. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 13 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0482.
- Atlantic City, NJ. International Audit Reports., 14 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0503.
- Hoboken, NJ., 15 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0510.
- Hoboken, NJ. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 16 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0511.
- Newark, NJ., 17 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0668.
- Newark, NJ. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 18 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0669.
- Brooklyn, NY., 19 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0789.
- Brooklyn, NY. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 20 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0790.
- Buffalo, NY., 21 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0832.
- Buffalo, NY. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 22 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0833.
- Buffalo, NY. International Audit Reports., 23 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0974.
- New York, NY., 24 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0880.
- New York, NY. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 25 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 0881.
- Philadelphia, PA., 26 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 1183.
- Philadelphia, PA. Jurisdiction., 27 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 1184.
- Philadelphia, PA. Correspondence., 1945-1969; 28 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 1268.
- Philadelphia, PA. Correspondence., 1970-1978; 29 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 1734.
- Philadelphia, PA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 30 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 2329.
- Philadelphia, PA. International Audit Reports., 31 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at location 2458.
- Portland, OR., 1 (Reel 20)
- Portland, OR. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 2 (Reel 20)
- Seattle, WA., 3 (Reel 20)
- Seattle, WA. Dispute with B.S.E.I.U., 1946-1947; 4 (Reel 20)
- Seattle, WA. Correspondence., 1947-1959; 5 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at location 0229.
- Seattle, WA. Wage Stabilization Case., 1951; 6 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at location 0618.
- Seattle, WA. Correspondence., 1960-1965; 7 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at location 0762.
- Seattle, WA. Correspondence., 1966; 8 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at location 1237.
- Seattle, WA. Correspondence., 1967-1969; 9 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at location 1661.
- Seattle, WA. Dispute with I.U.O.E., 1970-1971; 10 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at location 2102.
- Seattle, WA. (continued)., 1 (Reel 21)
- Seattle, WA. Correspondence., 1970-1972; 2 (Reel 21)
- Seattle, WA. Re: Department Store Agreement., 1972; 3 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 0370.
- Seattle, WA. Re: Department Store Agreement., 1973-1974; 4 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 0432.
- Seattle, WA. Minutes., 1973-1979; 5 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 0734.
- Seattle, WA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 6 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 1112.
- Seattle, WA. International Audit Reports., 7 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 1193.
- Spokane, WA., 8 (Reel 21)